# Hello everyone, I'm Wang Gang
# In this video I will share a home cooking
# Stir-fried pork with green pepper
# First we prepare 300g "Erjingtiao" chili pepper
# After removing the pepper cap, cut into roll blades for later use
# If you don't like spicy food, you can use a big green pepper instead
# Prepare a few "Xiaomila" and cut into small pieces for later use
# Prepare 2 garlic sprouts, and then cut them into small pieces diagonally.
# Prepare garlic and ginger, each 15 grams, and crush them for later use.
# The next step is to prepare the main ingredients
# Prepare 1 small piece of pork belly and cut into thin slices (about 150 g)
# You must cut the pork belly as thin as possible
# This makes it easier to stir-fry the lard
# Prepare a small piece of tenderloin and slice it against the grain for later use (about 100g)
# The purpose of adding tenderloin is to make this dish fat and even.
# Make it suitable for a wider population
# The next step is to prepare the cured tenderloin
# Add a pinch of salt to the bowl
# Add a little pepper
# Add 2 grams of light soy sauce
# Add 2 grams of egg white and stir well
# Add a little dry starch halfway through and mix well
# Adding dried starch can keep tenderloin tender but not firewood
# Finally add an appropriate amount of vegetable oil and mix well
# The purpose is to prevent clump
# Next step is fry
# First let's heat the wok
# After the wok is hot, fry the cutted peppers for 2 minutes
# The purpose of this step is to bring out pepper's aroma
# please remember that at this step, maintain moderate fire to prevent speculation.
# Stir the chili into a tiger skin and pour it out
# After the peppers are poured out, clean the wok and start frying the meat.
# First we preheat the wok
# After the wok is hot, add the appropritate amount of oil
# Pour out the hot oil afterwards
# Then stir-fry the cut pork belly for 1 minute
# The purpose of this step is to stir-fry pork belly for lard.
# It takes about 2 minutes if using family stove
# After 1 minute, stir-fry the marinated pork tenderloin a few times until it is medium well.
# Add chopped ginger and garlic in between
# The next step is to seasoning
# Add 6 grams of oyster sauce to the wok
# Add 4 grams of soy sauce
# Add a little sugar to refresh
# Add a little pepper
# Finally add dark soy 2g for color
# Add and stir-fry the processed peppers evenly afterwards.
# Finally, add the chopped garlic sprouts and stir-fry until they are softened.
# A very delicious homemade dish with small fried meat is done
# Technical summary below
First, the use of pork belly and tenderloin can make it fat and even.
Second, the savory pepper flavor is more farm-like
Third, this dish does not need salt, just need oyster sauce soy sauce for salty taste
The technical summary of the stir fried meat is completed